In fact when I got angry with him
De hecho cuando yo me enfadé con él hace
many years ago it was because of stacks that then
muchos años fue por stacks que luego
they had a time when they were friends and they did
ellos una época que encima fueron amigos
n't get along super badly in fact Fran told me
no se llevaban supermal de hecho me dijo
I'm not going to Andorra if Gref is
Fran yo no voy a andorra si está gref
around eh I mean I don't want to have anything to
por ahí eh o sea no quiero tener nada
do with it and in the end Well then I was doing
que ver y al final Bueno pues yo me iba
very well with Gref until I told him Hey
muy bien con gref hasta que le dije Oye
Fran gets upset that you make these
a Fran le molesta que hagas estos
comments without these pullit and I don't know what
comentarios sin estas pullit y no sé qué
because this bothers my friends don't do
porque esto le molesta a mis amigos no
it Don't mess with Fran Don't
lo hagas No te metas con Fran No te
mess with I don't know what and Willy did it
metas con no sé qué y lo hizo Willy
scolding Gref Hey Gref Behave yourself Don't
riñendo a gref Oye gref Pórtate bien No
post this or that because
pongas Esto ni Pongas lo otro que no te
my friends don't let you Before maybe you didn't know
dejan mis amigos antes igual no sabías
that it bothered me but now that you
que me molestaba pero ahora de que ya lo
know don't do it anymore and he did it again I
sabes no lo hagas más y lo volvió a
said well enough and on top of that he
hacer le dije pues hasta aquí y encima
calls me that night and says I've lost
él esa noche me llama y me dice Me he
internet at home I can't
quedado sin internet en casa no puedo
upload the video can I go to your house I'm
subir el vídeo puedo ir a tu casa estoy
angry now like I don't want to
enfadados ya en plan de que no quiero
know anything about you I said come on okay come on Of
saber nada de ti dije venga vale ven
course with time now I don't know if it
Claro yo con el tiempo ahora no sé si
was true  or not but I know that's it, up to
fue verdad o no pero sé que es el hasta
here I'll go one step further and cross the line. Let's
aquí voy un pasito más y cruzo la línea
see, bad person greev. I think that he has
A ver mala persona greev Yo creo que él
n't really done anything wrong, let's see, he's
no ha hecho realmente algo malo a ver ha
done his little [ __ ], screwed up. But I see it as
hecho sus cosillas [__] Pero yo lo veo
more about age. Would you dare to have
más cosas de la edad atreverías a hacer
a face-to-face with gref? Yes, I know that everything I
un cara a cara con gref sí se que todo
told him I can tell him again.
lo que le dije se lo puedo volver a